The Amanda Seale Show. Today's goes to Mother Nature. Last week was a wild time in the animal
kingdom. Yes, pun intended. Okay, so first off, we had army horses in London deciding that they
had enough of the military life, so they made a break for it, galloping through the streets,
but they were late for a tea party. Then a rogue elephant escaped from a circus and strolled
through the Montana streets. But wait, there's more. Three cows in Kansas escaped from a farm
and led the police on a hoof chase. These animals, I'm telling you, they know something that we don't.
It's game over. Now today's goes to a high school senior in Ohio named Ali. Someone handed her a bag
of tacky chips. I think it's Ali, actually. After a few munches, she saved two chips for later, tossed
the rest, headed to class. Next thing she knew, the principal hauled her into the office and gave
her a five-day suspension because apparently there's a no-corn policy due to the fact that
there's like a teacher at the school who has a severe allergy. They told her she couldn't go to
prom because of this. I feel like this is targeting because this just feels like somebody who was
waiting to do some wildness. Very tech. Nice. You win. You win. I was about to do it and you did it
before me and that's, listen. My bad. My bad. You got it. You got it. We are, we are, we are.